# **Ariso Okanga**

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

# **Highlighted Project**

#### Counter1-SMS: Scrum Master, Full stack developer

Link - https://github.com/Arisodee/COUNTER1-SMS

Description - This is a web application that allows users to send messages in bulk.

- Implemented the sms-sending feature using Africa's Talking API
- Worked on the UI for the Admin page.
- Merged the work done by the team members

# **Education**

# **Moringa School**

AUGUST 2020- FEB 2021

Full Stack Web Development

### **University of Nairobi**

MAY 2013 - DEC 2015

Master of Business Administration - Finance

# **Experience**

#### **Mellydee Cake House**

2016 - PRESENT

Baking and Decorating cakes, Social media marketing, Procurement and Accounting

## **Procurement Associate, Britam Insurance**

JAN 2016 - MAY 2016

#### **Socials**

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/imelda-ariso-0138995a/

Github: https://github.com/Arisodee

Tel: +254724565746

Email:arisodee@gmail.com

Portfolio: <a href="https://arisodee.github.io/">https://arisodee.github.io/</a>

#### **Personal Statement**

An enthusiastic, responsible and hardworking software developer. Having worked on different projects, I adapt to changes quickly, work well under pressure and adhere to strict deadlines. I work efficiently both in a team environment and individually.

## **Skills**

#### **Technical Skills**

HTML, CSS, Python (Django , Flask), Javascript, Angular, Bootstrap, Postgres.

#### **Personal Skills**

Adaptability, Team player, Detail oriented, Creativity, Presentation, Leadership, Organization.

## **Interests**

Baking Cycling Reading non-fiction books

#### **Languages**

English and Swahili

## References

Provided upon request